## Mina Nasr Esfahani

A highly motivated and Innovative individual is looking forward to be a part of Web development Web design team

#### **CAREER OBJECTVE**

Dedicated and self-motivated web designer with strong modern UI/UX design skills and working knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, CMS, and Adobe Creative Suite in a scrum team. Passionate to take creative ideas and concept development approaches. Professional in communicating with clients about project requirements and getting feedback, and two years of experience working as a customer service representative in a faced-paced environment.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Content Designer and Developer (Volunteer)**

03/2020-Present

IBO Reno Group- Brampton, Canada

- Worked in cooperation with the company manager in an agile environment to update the existing website
  on a frequent basis
- Worked with team members to create the content and design a brochure based on company requirement
- · Participated in online meetings with the manager and other team members throughout the process

## Web Designer and Developer (online)

01/2020-04/2020

Jaddeh Company-Montreal, Canada

- · Worked with the client to learn about the project requirements to create the mock-ups of the website
- Designed wireframes and prototypes and catalogs using XD, illustrator, and Adobe Photoshop
- Used various programming languages, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to optimize the company website
- Performed website tests and applied the feedback received from the users to ensure the quality assurance of the codes and design

# Customer Service Representative 05/2019-01/2020

Walmart-Toronto, Canada

- Helped 60+ customers daily both on phone and in person, with duties including performing transactions, returns, and presenting product information
- Communicated with managers and customers to solve the issues and customers' complaints
- Received customer satisfaction feedback, leading to receiving a letter of appreciation from the manager
- Reported the technical issues of the machines and computers to the manager

### **EDUCATION**

### Ontario Graduate Certificate, Web Development, and Internet Application

Conestoga College- Waterloo, Canada- GPA:3.84

12/2021

Relevant Courses: UI/UX Design Websites, Front End Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and WordPress), Back End Programming (PHP and MYSQL), Web Content Management (WordPress, Web Graphics and Prototyping (XD, Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop)

Bachelor's Degree, IT, Assessed by WES in Canada

Tabriz University- Tabriz, Iran

07/2014

### CMS (WordPress, Pantheon)

- Adobe Creative Suite
- UI/UX Design

# SKILLS Front-en

- Front-end and back-end programming
- Source-code editors (Notepad++, Atom, VS Code
- Strong Communicative Skills